[
    {
        "question": "1. What age did Florence have her first composition published?",
        "answers": {
            "a":	9,
            "b":	10,
            "c":	11,
            "d":	12
        },
        "correctAnswer": "c"
    },
    {
        "question": "2. Where did Florence receive her Bachelor of Music degree?",
        "answers": {
            "a":	"New England Conservatory",
            "b":	"Julliard",
            "c":	"Eastman", 
            "d":	"Curtis" 
        },
        "correctAnswer": "a"
    },
    {
        "question": "3. What was the name of the music teacher’s association that denied Florence admission?",
        "answers": {
            "a":	"Arkansas Music Teachers Association",
            "b":	"Chicago Music Teachers Association",
            "c":	"New York Music Teachers Association",
            "d":	"Los Angeles Music Teachers Association" 
        },
        "correctAnswer": "a"
    },
    {
        "question": "4. What was the name of Florence’s second husband?",
        "answers": {
            "a":	"Randy Johnson",
            "b":	"Scott Mills",
            "c":	"Daniel Williams",
            "d":	"Pusey Dell Arnett"            
        },
        "correctAnswer": "d"
    },
    {
        "question": "5. What was the name of the orchestra that performed her first symphony in 1933?",
        "answers": {
            "a":	"New York Philharmonic",
            "b":	"Chicago Symphony",
            "c":	"Los Angeles Philharmonic",
            "d":	"San Francisco Symphony"                        
        },
        "correctAnswer": "b"
    },
    {
        "question": "6. Which college did Florence NOT continue her education in? ",
        "answers": {
            "a":	"American Conservatory of Music",
            "b":	"Chicago Teachers College",
            "c":	"University of Maryland", 
            "d":	"Chicago Musical College"                         
        },
        "correctAnswer": "c"
    },
    {
        "question": "7. What does CMA stand for?",
        "answers": {
            "a":	"Charlotte Music Association",
            "b":	"Chicago Music Association",
            "c":	"Cabot Music Association",
            "d":	"Cadillac Music Association"                           
        },
        "correctAnswer": "b"
    },
    {
        "question": "8. Which way did Florence NOT earn a living?",
        "answers": {
            "a":	"Opera singer",
            "b":	"Sales from piano works",
            "c":	"Orchestrator for WGN radio",
            "d":	"Organist for silent films"                          
        },
        "correctAnswer": "a"
    },
    {
        "question": "9. Which conductor commissioned Florence to write a suite for strings?",
        "answers": {
            "a":	"Leonard Bernstein",
            "b":	"Pierre Boulez",
            "c":	"Herbert von Karajan",
            "d":	"Sir John Barbirolli"                            
        },
        "correctAnswer": "d"
    },
    {
        "question": "10. What year did Florence Price die from complications of a stroke?",
        "answers": {
            "a":	1950,
            "b":	1940,
            "c":	1960,
            "d":	1953                                       
        },
        "correctAnswer": "d"
    }
]